Interviewer: What are you doing in the UK?
Anna: In the UK, er, I just came for a visit.
I’m here the second time in my life, and it was always a dream of mine to come to London.
Er, yes.
Interviewer: Was there anything that surprised you about the UK when you arrived?
Anna: I think that the people are very open, and that, um, just everybody is so nice,
and I also saw some monuments and some places I wanted to see,
so I was also very impressed about the architecture, etc.
Interviewer: How do people in your country drive?
Madeleine: I think it depends where you are.
Where I live in Oregon, everything is very safe, much slower, but in New York City
everything is very fast, very dangerous.
Interviewer: Are you a typical driver for where you live?
Madeleine: I would say so, I d-, I’m a very cautious driver.
Interviewer: Do you have any ambitions for this year?
Chris: Um, yes, I’d like to visit my daughter in Australia,
and also plan towards my retirement.
Interviewer: Do you think you’re going to do them?
Chris: Certainly the planning, whether or not I achieve the visit is something else.
Interviewer: Have you ever seen a film more than three times?
Talitha: Yes, I really like Lord of the Rings, so I’ve definitely seen that more than three times.
Interviewer: What do you like about it?
Talitha: I love the scenery, um,
and I love the imagination.
Interviewer: What phone do you have?
Martin: I have an iPhone.
Interviewer: How old is it?
Martin: I believe, I believe my iPhone is now two years old.
Interviewer: How often do you change phones?
Martin: Um, I change phones maybe every three years.
Interviewer: What do you use it for the most?
Martin: I mostly use my phone for social media.